The book of love gets a rewrite.
'Tis the Season to be Merry is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Gary Yates.
Looking for a fresh angle to her book on relationships,
Merry heads to snow-covered Vermont.
She finds a new perspective and Christmas cheer
with charismatic aid worker Chris.
Merry Griffin, played by Rachael Leigh Cook.
Adam Walters, played by Travis Van Winkle.
Sonia Hendricks, played by Karen Malina White.
Darlene Walters, played by Amy Groening.
Joe Smith, played by Paul Essiembre.
Rose Walters, played by Lois Brothers.
Travis Scott Van Winkle (born November 4, 1982) is an American actor, best known for starring in the feature film Accepted (2006), the 2021 third season of the Netflix streaming television series You, portraying
Trent DeMarco in Transformers (2007), and Friday the 13th (2009), Lieutenant Danny Green in The Last Ship (2014–2018), and CIA operative Aldon Reese in the Netflix action comedy series FUBAR (2023–2025).
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.